Guide to the Pacific Improvement Company Records, 1869-1931 (inclusive), 1883-1927 (bulk) JL001
Department of Special Collections and University Archives
- Series 1. Business and Legal Papers
  - OAKLAND WATER FRONT COMPANY
    - Wilson -vs- OWFCo, 1918 (Box 24, Folder 177)
      - Legal documents
    - Ghiglione case, 1920 (Box 24, Folder 178)
      - Legal documents
    - Ghiglione case, 1920-21 (Box 24, Folder 179)
      - Legal documents
    - Ghiglione case, 1921 (Box 24, Folder 180)
      - Legal documents
    - Southern Pacific Claim, 1920 (Box 25, Folder 181)
    - J. Breunner and Company case, 1915-1917 (Box 25, Folder 182)
    - W.A. Boole and Sons, 1901-1916 (Box 25, Folder 183)
    - LeRoy case, 1920 (Box 25, Folder 184)
    - United States Shipping Board Emergency (Box 25, Folder 185)
    - Fleet Corporation, 1918-1919
      - Agreements
    - Building and dredging contracts, 1877-1919 (Box 25, Folder 186)
    - Income tax, [1913?] (Box 25, Folder 187)
    - Freighter information and miscellaneous business, no dates (Box 25, Folder 188)
    - Maxwell -vs- P.I. Co. and OWFCo., 1917 (Box 25, Folder 189)
  - MONTEREY COUNTY WATER WORKS
    - Carmel Development Company, 1922 (Box 25, Folder 190)
    - Bayside Fish affair, 1919 (Box 25, Folder 191)
    - Rocky Mountain Coal and Iron Company, 1907-1919 (Box 25, Folder 191a)
      - Agreements
      - Correspondence
  - EL VERANO IMPROVEMENT ASSOCIATION AND EL VERANO VILLA ASSOCIATION
    - Articles of Incorporation, 1891 (Box 25a, Folder 191b)
    - By laws, 1914
    - Minutes, 1914
    - Meeting notices, 1913-1915 (Box 25a, Folder 191c)
    - Stockholders, 1891-1914 (Box 25a, Folder 191)
      - Lists of shareholders
      - P.I.Co. shares
      - Stock certificates
    - Legal documents, 1890-1915 (Box 25a, Folder 191e)
      - Proxies
      - Resolutions
      - Indentures
    - Property data, map, no dates (Box 25a, Folder 191)
    - Miscellaneous (Box 25a, Folder 191g)
      - Sonoma Valley Improvement Co. Stock certificates, 1889-1890
      - Sonoma Valley Improvement Co. articles of incorporation, copy of original Sonoma Valley Imp. Co. Certificate of search, 1914 1888 1911
      - Verano Land Company articles of incorporation copy of original, 1914, 1888
  - MISCELLANEOUS PAPERS
    - Agreements, letters, notes, figures, 1877-1919 (Box 26, Folder 192)
    - Correspondence: C.P. Huntington and H.D. Money, 1882-1885 (Box 26, Folder 193)
    - Francis A. Fogg suit, 1884-1909 (Box 26, Folder 194)
      - Judicial settlement
    - Allegheny and Kinzua Railroad Co., 1892 (Box 26, Folder 195)
      - Printed summons
      - Complaint
      - Exhibits and injunction papers
    - Allegheny and Kinzua RR Co., 1895 (Box 26, Folder 196)
      - Bonds
    - Cochran -vs- P.I.Co. and others, 1906 (Box 26, Folder 197)
      - Legal documents
    - Bonds (Rome Decatur RR Co., Wightman Electric Manufacturing Co., Chesapeake, Ohio and Southwestern RR Co., Newport News and Mississippi Valley Co., Kentucky and South Atlantic RR Co.) (Box 26, Folder 198)
    - Olcott lands (Box 26, Folder 199)
    - Vulcan no. 2 Lode mining claim, 1918 (Box 26, Folder 200)
    - Notebook with lists of P.I.Co. subsidiaries and their directors, Payrolls, 1894-1904; 1901 (Box 26, Folder 201)
    - Index to minutes, dates burned (Box 26, Folder 202)
    - List of bondholders (black notebook), no dates (Box 26, Folder 203)
      - Liberty Bonds
- Series 2. Paid out Contracts, Deeds, Securities
  The CONTRACTS are arranged by number, and have been kept in this original order. There is an extremely rough progression in date (27-43).
  The DEEDS are arranged chronologically and pertain to Louisiana property. They are by the Pacific Improvement Company and theSSouthern Development Company, a subsidiary (44-47).
  The REGISTERS OF SECURITIES are bound volumes arranged chronologically (47a-i).
  DEED REGISTERS AND RECORDS are bound volumes recording d deeds and land ownership in various areas where the P.I.Co. owned land (48-54).
  - CONTRACTS
    - 1080-3995 (Box 27)
    - 4302-4540 (Box 28)
    - 4542-4920 (Box 29)
    - 4921-5295 (Box 30)
    - 5296-5649 (Box 31)
    - 5653-6020 (Box 32)
    - 6021-6440 (Box 33)
    - 6441-6885 (Box 34)
    - 6887-7386 (Box 35)
    - 7387-7865 (Box 36)
    - 7868-8360 (Box 37)
    - 8365-8737 (Box 38)
    - 8740-9220 (Box 39)
    - 9223-9334 (Box 40)
    - Alta Vista 3-123 (California)
    - Alta Vista 124-362 (Box 41)
    - Alta Vista 376-544 (Box 42)
    - Capay Valley Land Co. 108-477 (California)
    - Capay Valley Land Co. 478-565 and misc. contracts (Box 43)
  - DEEDS
    - El Verano Villa Association, 1-36 and miscellaneous deeds (California) (Box 43)
    - P.I.Co. Sundry deeds and papers with index, 1-112 and misc. deeds (Box 44)
    - P.I.Co. deeds, Louisiana property, 1893-1912 (Box 45)
    - Miscellaneous documents on Louisiana real estate, 1893-1903
    - P.I.Co. deeds, Louisiana property, 1912-1919 (Box 46)
    - Southern Development Company deeds, Louisiana property, 1883-1893
    - Southern Development Co. deeds, Louisiana property, 1893-1907 (Box 47)
  - SECURITIES
    - Register of Securities (bound), 1881-1888 (Volume 47a)
    - Register of Securities (bound), 1888-1889 (Volume 47b)
    - Register of Securities (bound), 1888-1891 (Volume 47c)
    - Register of Securities (bound), 1891-1893 (Volume 47)
    - Register of Securities (bound), 1894-1895 (Volume 47e)
    - Register of Securities (bound), 1896-1900 (Volume 47)
    - Register of Securities (bound), 1901-1912 (Volume 47g)
    - Register of Securities, Miscellaneous (bound), 1895-1899 (Volume 47h)
    - Register of Securities, Misc. (bound), 1899-1900 (Volume 47i)
  - DEED REGISTERS AND RECORDS (bound volumes)
    - Register of deeds, Brown and Coleman Counties, Texas, 1889-1905 (Volume 48)
    - Description and Location of Lands and Record of Deeds and Notes, 1881-1917 (Volume 49)
    - Town Lots in Texas, Record of Deeds and Notes, [1901?] (Volume 50)
    - Register of Deeds, Thomas H. Hubbard Lands, 1900-1908 (Volume 51)
    - Town Lot Receipts, April 1906-Feb 1908 (Volume 52)
    - Town Lot Receipts, March 1908-Dec 1909 (Volume 53)
    - Accounts: C.P. Huntington, 1879-1882 (Volume 54)
- Series 3. General Correspondence
  Includes a series of indexes of general letters, copybooks, and a large collection of general correspondence. Although quite routine in nature, this series is very complete; it covers twenty-six years of the company's existence, and much of the important California development took place during the years of this particular series of correspondence. Within the bulk of the correspondence, three definite sub-series were obvious and were preserved. A fourth was added for the remaining letters which fell into none of the first three patterns.
  Arrangement note
  The correspondence within folders is often arranged in reverse chronological order.
  - Subseries 1. Chronological Correspondence, 1901-1911
    This sub-series consists of a sequence of folders numbered from 1-373, each containing both incoming and outgoing letters of various subjects. General chronological progression.
    - 1-45b, 1901-1911 (Box 55)
    - 45c-63a, 1901-1911 (Box 56)
    - 63b-262, 1901-1911 (Box 57)
    - 263-373, 1906-1911 (Box 58)
  - Subseries 2. Alphabetic Correspondence
    The letters are arranged by author (incoming) and recipients (outgoing) in a numbered sequence of 12-199. Each folder has a second number on the right which corresponds to the folder in series A with that number. These letters are dated 1912-1919;a different arrangement was evidently begun around 1912,but the cross-reference pattern preserves the continuity of the correspondence.
    - 12-121, 1916-1919 (Box 58)
    - 123-199, 1915-1919 (Box 59)
  - Subseries 3. Numerical Correspondence, 1906-1926.
    Correspondence is arranged in sequences of numbered folders, each sequence of 1-100 covering a period of two to five months. An index to the subject of each folder is in the first folder of this series. Folders of the same number contain the same subject matter for any time period. This series is therefore arranged by subject and date simultaneously. The first six time periods, April 1906 to Sept. 1908contain no alphabetical index as a guide to the numbered folders. The remaining periods do, indicating letters received or sent, the date, and the number of the folder in which it can be found. Alphabetical by author and recipient.
    - (1-26), April-Aug, 1906 (Box 59)
    - (30-101), April-Aug, 1906 (Box 60)
    - (1-44), Sept-Dec, 1906
    - (51-101), Sept-Dec, 1906 (Box 61)
    - (1-30), Jan-April, 1907
    - (31-102), Jan-April, 1907 (Box 62)
    - (1-17), Nov 1907-Feb 1908
    - (20-98), Nov 1907-Feb 1908 (Box 63)
    - (1-13), March-June, 1908
    - (15-98), March-June, 1908 (Box 64)
    - (1-100), July-Sept, 1908 (Box 65)
    - (1-74), May-July, 1910 (Box 66)
    - (75-98), May-July, 1910 (Box 67)
    - (1-61), Nov 1910-Jan 1911
    - (63-99), Nov 1910-Jan 1911 (Box 68)
    - (1-70), May-July, 1911
    - (14-99), May-July, 1911 (Box 69)
    - (1-78), Aug-Oct, 1911
    - (82-98), Aug-Oct, 1911 (Box 70)
    - (1-98), April-June, 1912
    - (A-Q of index), Oct-Dec, 1912
    - (R-99), Oct-Dec, 1912 (Box 71)
    - (1-49), Jan-April, 1913
    - (50-98), Jan-April, 1913 (Box 72)
    - (1-37), April-June, 1913
    - (49-100), April-June, 1913 (Box 73)
    - (1-50), July-Sept, 1913
    - (52-98), July-Sept, 1913 (Box 74)
    - (1-50), Oct 1913-Jan 1914
    - (52-100), Oct 1913-Jan 1914 (Box 75)
    - (1-30), Jan-May, 1914
    - (37-98), Jan-May, 1914 (Box 76)
    - (1-9), May-Aug, 1914
    - (10-98), May-Aug, 1914 (Box 77)
    - (A-S of index), Sept 1914-Jan 1915
    - (T-98), Sept 1914-Jan 1915 (Box 78)
    - (A-M of index), Jan-April, 1915
    - (N-78), Jan-April, 1915 (Box 79)
    - (81-98), Jan-April, 1915 (Box 80)
    - (1-84), July-Sept, 1915
    - (97-98), July-Sept, 1915 (Box 81)
    - (1-70), Oct-Dec, 1915
    - (73-98), Oct-Dec, 1915 (Box 82)
    - (1-70), Jan-March, 1916
    - (76-99), Jan-March, 1916 (Box 83)
    - (1-83), April-June, 1916
    - (97-98), April-June, 1916 (Box 84)
    - (1-98), July-Sept, 1916
    - (1-98), Oct-Dec, 1916 (Box 85)
    - (A-S of index), Jan-March, 1917
    - (T-97), Jan-March, 1917 (Box 86)
    - (1-37), April-June, 1917
    - (50-97), April-June, 1917 (Box 87)
    - (1-63), July-Sept, 1917
    - (68-97), July-Sept, 1917 (Box 88)
    - (1-97), Oct-Dec, 1917
    - (A-R of index), Jan-April, 1918
    - (S-97), Jan-April, 1918 (Box 89)
    - (index), May-Sept, 1918
    - (1-100), May-Sept, 1918 (Box 90)
    - (A-H of index), Oct 1918-March 1919
    - (I-76), Oct 1918-March 1919 (Box 91)
    - (77-97), Oct 1918-March 1919 (Box 92)
    - (1-77), April-Dec, 1919
    - (77-97), April-Dec, 1919 (Box 93)
    - (1-98), 1920
    - (3-50), 1921
    - (53-97), 1921 (Box 94)
    - (6-84), 1922
    - (3-99), 1923
    - 1924 (Box 95)
    - 1925
    - 1926
  - Subseries 4. Sand delivery correspondence, 1919-1927
    This sub-series contains miscellaneous patterns of arrangement. Correspondence dealing with sand deliveries and the Hotel Del Monte from 1919-1927. The sand letters are in sequences of 1-150 in the case of the first two time periods; the third is numbered 120-300. The Hotel Del Monte letters are arranged in a pattern of 1-1, 1-2, etc., up to 8. The last two folders of the general correspondence contain maps, charts, pamphlets, and photographs which were included with the correspondence.
    - Sand Letters, (1-150), Jan-Dec, 1919 (Box 96)
    - Sand Letters, (1-16), Sept 1921-June 1922
    - Sand Letters, (17-150), Sept 1921-June 1922 (Box 97)
    - Sand Letters, (120-167), 1924 and 1925
    - Sand Letters, (170-284), 1924 and 1925 (Box 98)
    - Del Monte Properties, (1-1), 1927
    - Del Monte Properties, [(1-2)-8], 1927 (Box 99)
      General note
      NOTE: The last two folders of this box contain charts, pamphlets, maps, blueprints and photographs which were included with the general correspondence, but were of a general enough nature so that they could conveniently be gathered together at the end of the loose correspondence.
    - Copy book, letters, 1906-1913 (Volume 100)
    - Copy book, letters, 1913-1915 (Volume 101)
    - Scrapbook, 1921 (Volume 102)
      - Merced water situation
    - Index of general letters, Jan-April, 1907 (Volume 103)
    - Index of general letters, May-Oct, 1907 (Volume 104)
    - Index of general letters, Nov-1907-Feb 1908 (Volume 105)
    - Index of general letters, Mar-June, 1908 (Volume 106)
    - Index of general letters, July-Sept, 1908 (Volume 107)
    - Index of general letters, Oct 1908-Feb 1909 (Volume 108)
    - Index of general letters, Mar-May, 1909 (Volume 109)
    - Index of general letters, June-Aug, 1909 (Volume 110)
    - Index of general letters, Sept-Nov, 1909 (Volume 111)
- Series 4. Business Record Books, Many of the volumes in this series were badly burned and have been wrapped in brown paper. Most of these are in fair condition, but several are extremely fragile and were left in their wrapping. Those items with no dates are, for the most part, those in less than fair condition, and the dates were either burned beyond recognition, or the books were not opened and examined in order to preserve the paper.
  - PACIFIC IMPROVEMENT COMPANY
    - Daybook, June 1906-Aug 1911 (Volume 112)
    - Daybook, Sept 1911-Nov 1913 (Volume 113)
    - Daybook, Real Estate accounts, 1913 (Volume 114)
    - Cash Journal, 1887-1907 (Volume 115)
    - Cash Journal, 1906-1910 (Volume 116)
    - Cash Received, 1902-1905 (Volume 116a)
    - Journal, 1894-1904 (Volume 117)
    - Journal, 1904-1909 (Volume 118)
    - Journal, 1910-1919 (Volume 119)
    - Journal, 1904-1906 (Volume 120)
    - Journal: Renewals and Improvements, 1906-1912 (Volume 121)
    - Ledger: Renewals and Improvements, 1906-1912 (Volume 122)
    - Ledger, 1892-1894 (Volume 123)
    - Ledger, 1894-1896 (Volume 124)
    - Ledger, 1897-1899 (Volume 125)
    - Ledger, 1900-1902 (Volume 126)
    - Ledger, 1903-1905 (Volume 127)
    - Ledger, 1906-1908 (Volume 128)
    - Ledger, 1909-1912 (Volume 129)
    - Index to general ledger B (Volume 130)
    - Index to general ledger C (Volume 131)
    - Index to general ledger D (Volume 132)
    - Index to general ledger E (Volume 133)
    - Index to general ledger F (Volume 134)
    - Index to general ledger G (Volume 135)
    - Index to general ledger H (Volume 136)
    - Index to general ledger I (Volume 137)
    - Ledger, 1901-1905 (Volume 138)
    - Ledger, 1909-1910 (Volume 139)
    - Ledger, 1910-1916 (Volume 140)
    - Cash Book, 1883-1885 (Volume 141)
    - Cash Book, 1885-1887 (Volume 142)
    - Cash Book, 1888-1889 (Volume 143)
    - Cash Book, 1889 (Volume 144)
    - Cash Book, 1890-1891 (Volume 145)
    - Cash Book, 1891-1892 (Volume 146)
    - Cash Book, 1892-1893 (Volume 147)
    - Cash Book, 1893-1894 (Volume 148)
    - Cash Book, 1894-1896 (Volume 149)
    - Cash Book, 1896-1898 (Volume 150)
    - Cash Book, 1898-1900 (Volume 151)
    - Cash Book, 1900-1905 (Volume 152)
    - Cash Book, 1906-1911 (Volume 153)
    - Cash Book, 1911-1919 (Volume 154)
    - Cash Book, 1906-1907 (Volume 155)
    - Cash Book, 1907-1909 (Volume 156)
    - Cash Book, 1909-1911 (Volume 157)
    - Cash Book, 1911-1913 (Volume 158)
    - Cash Book, 1904 (Volume 159)
    - Timber Journal, 1891-1897 (Volume 160)
    - Timber Ledger, 1897-1899 (Volume 161)
    - Loans Payable, 1882-1883 (Volume 162)
    - Loans Payable, 1884-1888 (Volume 163)
    - Loans Payable, 1888-1892 (Volume 164)
    - Loans Payable, 1892-1894 (Volume 165)
    - Loans Payable, 1894-1895 (Volume 166)
    - Loans Payable, 1895-1896 (Volume 167)
    - Loans Payable, 1896-1897 (Volume 168)
    - Loans Payable, 1897-1899 (Volume 169)
    - Loans Payable, 1899-1900 (Volume 170)
    - Loans Payable, 1892-1900 (Volume 171)
    - Loans and Bills Payable, 1893-1900 (Volume 172)
    - Loans Receivable, 1881-1882 (Volume 173)
    - Loans Receivable, 1882-1883 (Volume 174)
    - Loans Receivable, 1893-1907 (Volume 175)
    - Bills Rendered, 1901-1905 (Volume 176)
    - Accounts Receivable, 1917-1926 (Volume 177)
    - General Records, 1914-1917 (Volume 178)
    - Chart of company accounts, no date (Volume 178a)
    - San Francisco Cash Abstracts, July-Dec 1900 (Volume 179)
    - San Francisco Cash Abstracts, Jan-June 1901 (Volume 180)
    - San Francisco Cash Abstracts, July-Dec 1901 (Volume 181)
    - San Francisco Cash Abstracts, Jan-June 1902 (Volume 182)
    - San Francisco Cash Abstracts, July-Dec 1902 (Volume 183)
    - San Francisco Cash Abstracts, Jan-June 1903 (Volume 184)
    - San Francisco Cash Abstracts, July-Dec 1903 (Volume 185)
    - San Francisco Cash Abstracts, July-Dec 1909 (Volume 186)
    - San Francisco Cash Abstracts, Jan-June 1910 (Volume 187)
    - San Francisco Cash Abstracts, July-Dec 1910 (Volume 188)
    - San Francisco Cash Abstracts, Jan-June 1913 (Volume 189)
    - San Francisco Cash Abstracts, July-Dec 1913 (Volume 190)
    - San Francisco Cash Abstracts, Jan-June 1914 (Volume 191)
    - San Francisco Cash Abstracts, July-Dec 1914 (Volume 192)
    - San Francisco Cash Abstracts, Jan-June 1915 (Volume 193)
    - San Francisco Cash Abstracts, July-Dec 1915 (Volume 194)
    - San Francisco Cash Abstracts, 1906-1908 (Volume 195)
    - San Francisco Cash Abstracts, 1908-1909 (Volume 196)
    - San Francisco Cash Abstracts, 1909-1911 (Volume 197)
    - San Francisco Cash Abstracts, 1911-1913 (Volume 198)
    - San Francisco Cash Abstracts, 1913-1914 (Volume 199)
    - San Francisco Cash Abstracts, 1914-1915 (Volume 200)
    - San Francisco Cash Abstracts, 1917-1919 (Volume 201)
    - Journal Abstract, San Francisco, 1906-1913 (Volume 202)
    - New York Cash Abstracts, 1906-1913 (Volume 203)
    - New York Cash Abstracts, 1906 (Volume 203a)
    - New York Cash Abstracts, 1906-1907 (Volume 203b)
    - New York Cash Abstracts, 1907-1908 (Volume 203c)
    - New York Cash Abstracts, 1908-1909 (Volume 204)
    - New York Cash Abstracts, 1909-1911 (Volume 205)
    - New York Cash Abstracts, 1911-1919 (Volume 206)
    - New York Cash Abstracts, 1902-1904 (Volume 207)
    - New York Cash Abstracts, 1904-1906 (Volume 208)
    - New York Cash Abstracts, 1906-1908 (Volume 209)
    - New York Cash Abstracts, 1908-1910 (Volume 210)
    - New York Cash Abstracts, 1910-1911 (Volume 211)
    - Journal Abstract, New York, 1897-1906 (Volume 212)
    - Financial Statements, 1916 (Volume 213)
    - Financial Statements, 1917 (Volume 214)
    - Financial Statements, 1918 (Volume 215)
    - Financial Statements, 1919 (Volume 216)
    - Comparative financial statement, 1914-1918 (Volume 216a)
    - Accountant's report, 1913 (Volume 217)
    - Monthly and annual reports, 1916-1917 (Box 218, Folder 1-24)
      - Annual, 1 volume May-Nov, 1915-
      - Annual, 2 volumes Jan-Oct, 1916-
      - Annual, 2 volumes Jan-May, 1917-
    - Monthly and annual reports, 1917-1919 (Box 219, Folder 25-42)
      - June-Oct, 1917-
      - Annual, 2 volumes Jan-Oct, 1918-
      - 1919-Jan-June
    - Bank of America check stub books, 12 volumes, 1903-1909 (Volume 220)
    - Bank of America check stub books, 10 volumes, 1910-1919 (Volume 221)
    - Checkbooks, 4 volumes, 1907-1917 (Volume 222)
    - Insurance, 1907-[1916?] (Volume 223)
    - Insurance Register, 1918 (Volume 224)
    - Index of vouchers, (wooden box), 1914-1924 (Volume 225)
    - Voucher register, 1909-1913 (Volume 226)
    - Addenda: Voucher register, 1906-09 (Volume 226a)
    - Voucher register, 1913 (Volume 227)
    - Cash vouchers, July 1906-July 1907 (Volume 228)
    - Cash vouchers, Aug 1907-May 1908 (Volume 229)
    - Cash vouchers, May 1908-May 1909 (Volume 230)
    - Cash vouchers, May 1909-May 1910 (Volume 231)
    - Cash vouchers, June 1910-July 1911 (Volume 232)
    - Cash vouchers, July 1911-Aug 1912 (Volume 233)
    - Cash vouchers, Sept 1912-July 1913 (Volume 234)
    - Cash vouchers, Oct 1913-March 1914
    - Cash vouchers, March 1914-April 1915 (Volume 235)
    - Cash vouchers, May 1915-Dec 1915 (Volume 236)
    - Vouchers, Jan-Feb 1913
    - Cash and Journal Vouchers, 1914-1919 (Volume 237)
    - Vouchers, Feb-March 1913 (Volume 238)
    - Vouchers, March-April 1913 (Volume 239)
    - Vouchers, April-May 1913 (Volume 240)
    - Vouchers, June-July 1913 (Volume 241)
    - Vouchers, July-Aug 1913 (Volume 242)
    - Vouchers, Aug-Sept 1913 (Volume 243)
    - Vouchers, Sept-Nov 1913 (Volume 244)
    - Vouchers, Dec 1913-May 1914 (Volume 245)
    - Vouchers, June-Dec 1914 (Volume 246)
    - Vouchers, Dec 1914-June 1915 (Volume 247)
    - Vouchers, July 1915-Oct 1915 (Volume 248)
    - Vouchers, Oct 1915-Feb 1916 (Volume 249)
    - Vouchers, Feb-June 1916 (Volume 250)
    - Vouchers, June-Sept 1916 (Volume 251)
    - Vouchers, Sept 1916-Jan 1917 (Volume 252)
    - Vouchers, Jan-May 1917 (Volume 253)
    - Vouchers, May-Aug 1917 (Volume 254)
    - Vouchers, Aug-Dec 1917 (Volume 255)
    - Vouchers, Dec 1917-May 1918 (Volume 256)
    - Vouchers, May-Oct 1918 (Volume 257)
    - Vouchers, Oct 1918-April 1919 (Volume 258)
    - Vouchers, April 1919-May 1920 (Volume 259)
    - Vouchers, May 1920-Nov 1921 (Volume 260)
    - Vouchers, Nov 1921-Nov 1923 (Volume 261)
    - Vouchers, Nov 1923-April 1926 (Volume 262)
    - Vouchers, April 1926-Dec 1928 (Volume 263)
    - Hotel Del Monte Vouchers, Dec 1913
    - Geary Street Park and Ocean Ry Co. Vouchers, Oct 1913-Jan 1923
    - Land Department Vouchers; new books, Oct 1913-Nov 1915 (Volume 264)
    - Journal Vouchers, Dec 1910-Sept 1914 (Volume 265)
    - Journal Vouchers, Oct 1914-Oct 1916 (Volume 266)
    - Journal Vouchers, Oct 1916-Dec 1917 (Volume 267)
    - Journal Vouchers, Dec 1917-Jan 1919 (Volume 268)
    - Journal Vouchers, Jan 1919-June 1924 (Volume 269)
    - Journal Vouchers, July 1924-Dec 1928 (Volume 270)
    - New York Office Journal Vouchers, Dec 1912-Dec 1917
    - Tax Vouchers, 1909
    - Tax Vouchers, 1910-1912 (Nov) (Volume 271)
    - Tax Vouchers, 1912-1914 (Volume 272)
    - Tax Receipts, 1915
    - Tax Vouchers, 1915-1916 (Nov) (Volume 273)
    - Tax Vouchers, 1916-1918 (Nov) (Volume 274)
    - Tax Vouchers, 1918-1920 (Volume 275)
    - Statements of overcharges on shipments, 1906-1909 (Volume 276)
  - ALTA VISTA TRACT (CALIFORNIA)
    - Transfer Ledger, 1914-1922 (Volume 277)
  - CAPAY VALLEY LAND COMPANY (CALIFORNIA)
    - By laws, 1887 (Volume 278)
    - By laws, amended, 1907 (Volume 279)
    - Minutes, 1887-1904 (Volume 280)
    - Minutes, 1906-1920 (Volume 281)
    - Stock Certificates (Volume 282)
    - Stock Certificates (Volume 283)
    - Stock Journal (Volume 284)
    - Stock Journal, 1894-1920 (Volume 285)
    - Stock Ledger (Volume 286)
    - Journal, 1906-1909 (Volume 287)
    - Journal, 1910-1918 (Volume 288)
    - Journal, 1918-1920 (Volume 289)
    - Cactus Ledger, 1918-1920 (Volume 290)
    - Ledger, 1906-1909 (Volume 291)
    - Ledger, 1915-1920 (Volume 292)
    - Cash Book, 1887-1897 (Volume 293)
    - Cash Book, 1886-1915 (Volume 294)
  - CARBON HILL COAL COMPANY (WASHINGTON STATE)
    - Stock Certificates (Volume 295)
    - Minutes, 1880-1904 (Box 295a, Folder 1)
    - By laws, 1880 (Box 295a, Folder 2)
    - Stock Ledger (Box 295a, Folder 3)
    - Transfer Journal (Box 295a, Folder 4)
    - Financial Reports, 1910 (Box 295a, Folder 5)
    - Financial Reports, May-Aug 1911 (Box 295a, Folder 6)
    - Financial Reports, Sept-Nov 1911 (Box 295a, Folder 7)
    - Mining Reports, no dates (Box 295a, Folder 8)
    - Mining Reports, 1914-1915 (Box 295b, Folder 9)
    - Mining Reports, Jan-Aug 1916 (Box 295b, Folder 10)
    - Mining Reports, Sept-Dec 1916 (Box 295b, Folder 11)
    - Mining Reports, Jan-March 1917 (Box 295b, Folder 12)
    - Mining Reports, March-Dec 1917 (Box 295b, Folder 13)
    - Mining Reports, Jan-April 1918 (Box 295b, Folder 14)